{
    "id": "5d7dc06ebef640a09cb848229a0843b3",
    "title": "Simple Past Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ………………… Joe in the morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "met",
                "have met",
                "had met"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………. recognize me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "didn't",
                "doesn't",
                "hasn't"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………… out of the window.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has looked",
                "looked",
                "had looked"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Peter ………………. another window yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was breaking",
                "broke",
                "has broken"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Deceived by his friends, he ………………. all hope.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lost",
                "has lost",
                "had lost"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher ………………… the boy for misbehaving in the class.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has punished",
                "punished",
                "had punished"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The cat …………….. all the milk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "had drunk",
                "has drunk",
                "drank"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The bell ………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rung",
                "has rung",
                "rang"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The sailor ……………….. with the sinking ship.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has stayed",
                "had stayed",
                "stayed"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy …………………. if he could have another piece of cake.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has asked",
                "asked",
                "had asked"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}